# **Daniel Arbon**

Phone: **0422 735 715** 

Email: danieltarbon@live.com.au
Location: Adelaide, South Australia
GitHub: https://github.com/arbdt

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-arbo

n-9bbb2419a/

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a web developer with experience creating both front-end and back-end. I have a certificate in Full Stack Web Development from Adelaide University, and a Bachelor of Information Technology from the University of South Australia. I have experience in generating HTML, CSS, and JavaScript; with utilising AJAX-based API calls and with implementing the Bootstrap responsive framework. I also have experience with using Git and GitHub for version control.

From previous work experience outside of the web development sector, I have had many opportunities to engage in and hone my skills at teamwork for projects, both as a participant in terms of managing team members and tasks. Work and educational scenarios have given me a good foundation and understanding of the dynamics of customer relations and working with a client.

### **EXAMPLES**

# International Space Station Tracker, <a href="https://github.com/arbdt/bcs-project-1">https://github.com/arbdt/bcs-project-1</a>

HTML, CSS, JS

- A website that makes use of JSON from APIs to display International Space Station data such as location, altitude, speed and day/night side of the planet
- The location is displayed on an embedded Google Map
- The day/night information is used to determine a light or dark theme for the page
- Semantic UI is used for styling

# Workday Schedule Planner, https://github.com/arbdt/work-day-scheduler

HTML, CSS, JS

- A website that allows users to view and set event during work day hours
- Entries are stored in browser local storage
- Moment.js is used for determining current time of day and colouring the entries accordingly

# Javascript Code Quiz, <a href="https://github.com/arbdt/code-quiz">https://github.com/arbdt/code-quiz</a>

HTML, CSS, JS

- A website that makes use of JavaScript to deliver a short five-question quiz about JavaScript
- Time remaining upon completion is used as a score and saved in local storage

## **SKILLS**

- Web development with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Mobile Application development with Java and Swift

- Programming in Java, Python, C++, C#, and ASP.net
- Proficiency with JQuery, Bootstrap, Ajax
- Informal technical support and training experience
- Effective communication and teamwork
- Customer service and client interaction
- Proficient with Microsoft Windows and Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Powerpoint)
- Administrative duties and report writing
- Providing informal technical support and training to others
- Time management

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Volunteer, Resthaven Onkaparinga Community Services

2020 - present

• Assisting with the provision of social activities for older people

# Technical Support, Self-employed

2015 - present

- Phone and on-site technical support of Windows PC, Apple IOS and Android devices
- Installation of new hardware and software
- Set-up and troubleshooting of home networks

# Research Assistant, Torrens Resilience Institute

2012 - 2013

- Data collection
- Writing of reports

# Administration Assistant (contractual), Torrens Resilience Institute

2012

- Start and end of day office procedures
- Received goods and documents
- Answered and directed phone calls and queries
- Operated as a private contractor

# Laboratory Assistant, Flinders Medical Centre

2010

- Organised stock orders
- Data entry

# **Refill Assistant, Big W**

2008 - 2009

- Stock replenishment
- Tidying shelves
- Assisting customers with enquiries

## **EDUCATION**

# Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp, University of Adelaide

2020 - 2021

- Currently being undertaken
- Subjects include: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax APIs, Node.js

## Bachelor of Information Technology, University of South Australia

2016 - 2018

- Majors: Mobile App Development, Software Development
- Subjects included: Java, C++, .Net, Unix, Visual Studio, Project Management (PRINCE2 framework), System Analysis and Design, Interface Design, Data Structures, Android Studio, XCode, Swift

# **Diploma of Information Technology,** South Australian Institute of Business and Technology

2015 - 2015

• Subjects included: Python, Java, IT Fundamentals, Network Fundamentals

# Bachelor of Nursing, Flinders University

2013 - 2014

• Included 2 placements at major metropolitan hospitals

# Graduate Diploma in Plant Health and Biosecurity, University of Adelaide

2011 - 2011

# Bachelor of Science, Flinders University

2007 - 2010

Majors: Molecular Biology, Microbiology

## **REFERENCES**

Elizabeth Vuong

0401 416 672

## Professor Paul Arbon

0418 856 560

Director, Torrens Resilience Institute